RG 005:033, Office of the Governor: Abraham Ribicoff (1955-1961)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Subject Files
  - Industrial Sites in Hartford County – Conn[ecticut] Industrial Development Council [Note: Sent to Cat[alogue] Dep[artmen]t JHR], 1959 (Box 661)
  - Ingraham, E. Company, Bristol, Conn[ecticut] (Box 661)
  - Insurance (Box 661)
  - Insurance Department, 3 folders (Box 661)
  - Insurance Dep[artmen]t re: Veto Insurance Tax Bills (Box 661)
  - Inter-Governmental Cooperation, Commission on, 1955-1957; 1 binder (Box 661)
  - Inter-Governmental Relations Subcommittee, L. H. Fountain, Chairman (Box 661)
  - Interim Committees of the 1959 G[eneral] A[ssembly], Propositions being Studied by (Box 661)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, Washington, D. C. (Box 661)
  - Interstate Compacts on Highway Safety re: Congressman John V.Beamer’s Resolution H. J. 221 (Box 661)
  - Interstate Route 95 (Box 661)
  - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 3 folders (Box 661)
  - Investment Committee (Box 661)
  - Iowa – Connecticut (Box 661)
  - Italian Ambassador (Manlio Brasio) (Box 661)
  - James Blackstone Memorial Library Assoc[iation] (Box 661)
  - Japanese Imports re: Silverware M[anu]f[acturin]g Industry in the United States (Box 661)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (Senator) for President (Box 661)
  - Jonathan Trumbull Polaris Submarine (Box 661)
  - Judges – (Circuit Court) (Box 661)
  - Judges – Minor Courts, Conn[ecticut] Supreme Court, Superior and Common Pleas Courts (Box 661)
  - Judicial (Box 662)
  - Judicial Council (Box 662)
  - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 662)
  - Kent House re: Purchase of Property in Greenwich, Conn[ecticut] (Box 662)
  - Korean Bonus [for Veterans] (Box 662)
  - Kowalski, Frank (Col[onel]) re: Congressman at Large Nomination (Box 662)
  - Labor, State Department of, 5 folders (Box 662)
  - Labor, Department of, Washington, D.C. (Box 662)
  - Labor Legislation (Box 662)
  - Labor Relations, State Board of (Box 662)
  - Labor Relations Board, State (Box 662)
  - Landers [Management Company] [strike] (Box 663)
  - Lantern Hill Road Bridge over Long Pond (North Stonington and Ledyard) re: request of Mr. W[illia]m J. Cedzich (Box 663)
  - Laurel Heights Sanatorium (Box 663)
  - Lee, Richard C. (Mayor) [New Haven] re: his proposal for “Sit – Outs” (Box 663)
  - Leffingwell Inn, Norwich, Conn[ecticut] (Box 663)
  - Legally Liable Relatives (Box 663)
  - Legislation Approved by Governor Ribicoff, 1959 General Assembly (Box 663)
  - Legislative Commissioner (Robert A. Wall), 2 folders (Box 663)
  - Legislative Council (Box 663)
  - Legislative Reform (Box 663)
  - Library, State, 3 folders (Box 663)
  - Lime Rock Sports Car Track (Box 663)
  - Lions Club Highway Safety Program (Box 663)
  - Liquor (Box 663)
  - Liquor Control Commission (Box 663)
  - Liquor – Early Closing, Against (Box 663)
  - Liquor – Early Closing, For (Box 663)
  - Litter (Litterbug and Litterbog) (Box 663)
  - Long Lane School, 2 folders (Box 663)
  - Mansfield State Training School & Hospital, 2 folders (Box 663)
  - Manufacturers Association of Connecticut (Box 663)
  - Marine Commercial Fisheries Commission, Conn[ecticut] (Box 663)
  - M A R K – Norwalk Weekly Magazine (Box 663)
  - Maternal Care Adoption Services, Inc., Lakeville, Conn[ecticut] re: Dr. Eleanor Hamilton (Box 664)
  - Mediation & Arbitration, Board of (Box 664)
  - Meet the Press re: Governor Ribicoff [appeared on the program on May 18, 1960, Miami Beach] (Box 664)
  - Memberships, 2 folders (Box 664)
  - Mental Health, 2 folders (Box 664)
  - Mental Health Budget (Box 664)
  - Mental Health, Dep[artmen]t of, 3 folders (Box 664)
  - Mental Health, State Dep[artmen]t of – Annual Reports and Other Reports re: Mental Health (Box 664)
  - Mental Health, State Dep[artmen]t of – Monthly Newsletter (Box 664)
  - Mental Health (National Committee) (Box 664)
  - Meriden re: Relocation of Route U.S. 6 – A and U.S. 5 (Box 664)
  - Meriden Industry Action Commission (Box 664)
  - Merritt Parkway (Box 665)
  - Merritt Parkway Commission (Box 665)
  - Methodism – The Methodist Church (Box 665)
  - Middletown – Interstate Highway 91 re: access road (Box 665)
  - Middletown Vocational Technical School (Box 665)
  - Mid-Fairfield Child Guidance Center (Box 665)
  - Milford (Box 665)
  - Milford Charter Bill (Box 665)
  - Military Department (Adjutant General), 2 folders (Box 665)
  - Milk, 3 folders (Box 665)
  - Motor Vehicles (Box 665)
  - Motor Vehicles Dep[artmen]t, 4 folders (Box 665)
  - Motorola Radio Towers re: Second Hill residents of Bridgewater, Conn[ecticut] re: Highway Dep[artmen]t communications system (Box 665)
  - Mystic Oral School for the Deaf, 3 folders (Box 665)
  - N[ational] A[ssociation] for the A[dvancement] of C[olored] P[eople] (New Haven Chapter Freedom Fund Drive Kick – Off Honoring Gov[ernor] Ribicoff), 1958 September 21 (Box 666)
  - Narcotics (Box 666)
  - National Resources Conference: Nov[ember] 26, 1956 [– December 7, 1956, at Trinity College, Hartford, Conn[ecticut]; Bridgeport, Conn[ecticut], May 12 – 23, 1958 (Box 666)
  - Natural Gas (Box 666)
  - Natureopathic Examiners, Board of (Box 666)
  - Naugatuck Armory (Box 666)
  - Naugatuck Valley River Flood Control Commission (Box 666)
  - Naval Shore Patrols re: their discontinuances (Box 666)
  - New England Council (Box 666)
  - New England Governors’ Conference, 2 folders (Box 666)
  - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control Commission (Box 666)
  - New England – New York Inter-Agency Committee (Box 666)
  - New Haven Annex (Box 666)
  - New Haven Bills (Box 666)
  - New Haven Citizens Action [Commission] (Box 666)
  - New Haven County Home (Box 666)
  - Newington Home for Crippled Children (Box 666)
  - New London and Hartford, Report on Modern Highway Between, by Alfred Kaehrle Associates, Dec[ember], 1958 (Box 666)
  - New London Armory (Nat[iona]l Guard) (Box 666)
  - New London, Port of (Box 666)
  - New London – Route 1 (Box 666)
  - New London Turnpike (Box 666)
  - Newton Chamber of Commerce – Route 25 (Box 666)
  - New York Authority, Port of (Congressional Investigation) (Box 666)
  - New York State Income Tax re: Correspondence between Gov[ernor] Ribicoff and Attorney Roswell Magill (Box 667)
  - Noank Lobster Hatchery (Box 667)
  - Norwich Party Label Bill (Box 667)
  - Norwich State Hospital (Box 667)
  - Northeastern Forest Fire Protection Commission (Box 667)
  - Nurses Scholarship Aid (Box 667)
  - Nursing, Board of Examiners for (Box 667)
  - Nursing, B[oar]d of (Box 667)
  - Oak Street Connector – Mayor Richard Lee [New Haven] (Box 667)
  - Oakwood Acres Project (Box 667)
  - Old Age (Box 667)
  - Old People’s Village, Committee to Study Need for, at New Britain Memorial Hospital (Box 667)
  - Opticians, Commission on, 2 folders (Box 667)
  - Optometry (Box 667)
  - Optometry, Board of Examiners in (Box 667)
  - Osteopathic Examining Board (Box 667)
  - Parade Magazine (Box 667)
  - Park & Forest Commission (Box 667)
  - Parole, Board of (Box 667)
  - Parsells, Norman K. – [U.S.] State Dep[artmen]t (Box 667)
  - Passing Zones (Double Lines on Highway) (Box 667)
  - Personnel Appeal Board, 2 folders (Box 667)
  - Personnel Dep[artmen]t, 4 folders (Box 667)
  - Pharmacy (Box 668)
  - Pharmacy Commission (Box 668)
  - Physically Handicapped – Conn[ecticut] Gov[ernor]’s Committee and Physically Handicapped Week (Box 668)
  - Physically Handicapped, Employment of (Box 668)
  - Physical Therapists, Board of Examiners, 2 folders (Box 668)
  - Pine Orchard Harbor, Branford (Box 668)
  - Police Training Program (Box 668)
  - Polio Vaccine, 2 folders (Box 668)
  - “Port Commission, A Brief on An Act Concerning the Creation and Establishment of a Connecticut,” [by Arthur H. Gosselin] S. B. 694, H. B. 1782, 1955 (Box 668)
  - Portrait (Box 668)
  - Portrait Presentation, 1961 April 3 (Box 668)
  - President’s Committee on Scientists and Engineers – Yale University, New Haven, 1958 February 3-4 (Box 668)
  - Primary [S. B. 135; An Act Concerning Nominating Procedures], 1955 (Box 668)
  - Prince, Albert I., Technical School (Box 668)
  - Prison Association (Connecticut) (Box 668)
  - Prison Reform (Box 668)
  - Private Employment Agencies P. A. 640, 1959 G[eneral] A[ssembly] (Box 668)
  - Psychiatric Services at Conn[ecticut] School for Boys, Long Lane School & Connecticut Reformatory (Box 668)
  - Psychiatric Treatment and Research Center (Box 668)
  - Psychologists, Board of Examiners of, 2 folders (Box 668)
  - Public Utilities (Box 668)
  - Public Utilities Commission, 2 folders (Box 668)
  - Public Works (Box 669)
  - Public Works Dep[artmen]t [6 folders; half the box] (Box 669)
  - Railroad Crossings [Unguarded] (Box 669)
  - Railroad Industry (Box 669)
  - Rainmaker – Attorney General Bracken’s Opinion to Gov[ernor] Ribicoff and Correspondence re: Rainmaker [Plan to seed clouds in order to produce rain] (Box 669)
  - Rakoczi Aid Association & Verhovay Fraternal Insurance Assoc[iation] Merger (Box 669)
  - Redevelopment Committee – Minutes (Box 669)
  - Refugee Relief Program (Box 669)
  - Regional Planning Committee – Mr. William H. Putnam, Chairman (Box 669)
  - Regional Planning Conference, Hotel Statler, Hartford, Conn[ecticut], 1957 June 11 (Box 670)
  - Rent Control [Letters For and Against], 13 folders (Box 670)
  - Rent Control Letters Not in Favor of Retention of Controls: answered by form letter (Box 671)
  - Rent Control (Box 671)
  - Reorganization [State Government] (Box 671)
  - Representatives in Congress, Acceptances [Of official letters from the Governor informing them of the results of elections] (Box 671)
  - Reprieves (Box 671)
  - Retarded Children, 3 folders (Box 671)
  - Rewards, Offer of (Box 671)
  - Rhode Island Naval Base re: Traffic Accidents involving Naval Personnel (Box 671)
  - Rifles, Surplus Military re: Increasing Imports Threaten To Impair the Nat[iona]l Security: Petition of American Sporting Arms [Manufacturers] (Box 671)
  - Right to Work [Opinions for and against a bill before the General Assembly] (Box 671)
  - Roaring Brook – Walnut Street Watershed, Connecticut Project (Box 671)
  - Rocket Launching by High School Students (Box 671)
  - “The Road Toll,” The Travelers 1958 Book of Street and Highway Accident Data (Box 671)
  - Route 5, Location of (Box 671)
  - Route 5, Location of – Hamden and North Haven (Box 671)
  - Route 5, Location of (Box 671)
  - Route 5, Relocation of (Hamden, New Haven and North Haven) (Box 671)
  - Route 6 (Box 671)
  - Sales Tax (Box 672)
  - Saturday Evening Post – Article by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff: Correspondence Received (Box 672)
  - Savings Bank Life Insurance Trustees & Savings Bank Railroad Investment Committee (Box 672)
  - Scholarships, State (Box 672)
  - School Appearances (Box 672)
  - School Bus Bill (Box 672)
  - School Buses [School Bus Law] (Box 672)
  - School for Boys, Meriden (Box 672)
  - Scissors and Shears (re: tariff reduction) (Box 672)
  - Seaside Hospital (Box 672)
  - Secretary of the State [Connecticut] (Box 672)
  - Security Treatment Center for the Diagnosis, Custody, Care and Treatment of Certain Mentally Ill, Mentally Deficient or Emotionally Unbalanced Persons Who Have Been Convicted of an Offense (Box 672)
  - Segregation (Box 672)
  - Selective Service System (Box 672)
  - Senate, U. S. – Democratic Nominee – [Opinions About], 1958 (Box 672)
  - Sex Deviates [Re: George Davies’ sex crimes in Waterbury. Includes petitions.] (Box 672)
  - Sheehan Bill [S. A. 374 S. B. 966 An Act Granting an Embalmer’s License to Richard W. Sheehan] (Box 672)
  - Shell Fish Commission (Box 672)
  - Shelton, Bureau of Purchase S.A. 516 (Box 672)
  - Shepaug Reservoir Bill Pro and Con (Box 672)
  - Shepaug Water Tower Project (Box 672)
  - Sherwood Island [4 folders], 4 folders (Box 672)
  - Silvermine Community Assoc[iation], Inc., Norwalk, Conn[ecticut] re: Relocation of Route 7 (Box 672)
  - Slaughterhouse Bills (Box 672)
  - Slum Clearance and Urban Development Conference, State Capitol, [Called by Senator Prescott Bush to discuss Federal Housing Act of 1954], 1955 March 28 (Box 673)
  - Small Business Administration (Box 673)
  - Small Loans, Rate of Interest – P. A. 636 Vetoed (Box 673)
  - Soldiers’, Sailors’ and Marines’ Fund (Box 673)
  - Southbury Training School (Box 673)
  - Special Session – House and Senate Bills Introduced, 1958 March 4 (Box 673)
  - Special Session (Flood Control) Subjects for possible inclusion on Agenda of (Box 673)
  - Special Session Legislation (Box 673)
  - Special Session, 1957 (Box 673)
  - Speeding, 7 folders (Box 673)
  - Speeding – Republican Platform Plank (Box 673)
  - Springfield Ordinance District (Box 673)
  - Stamford, City of, Housing Problems re: Conn[ecticut] Turnpike Displacement of Families (Box 673)
  - Stamford, City of – Pacific Street and Underpass (Box 673)
  - Stamford Reserve Armory (Box 673)
  - Stamford Water Company re: petition rec[eive]d by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff (Box 673)
  - State Editor, Office of [Editor of Judicial Department publications] (Box 673)
  - State Employee [Connecticut State Employee Association] (Box 673)
  - State Employees’ Retirement Commission (Box 673)
  - State Farm and Prison for Women (Box 673)
  - Spanish War Veterans, United (Box 674)
  - State Fiscal Study Commission, 1 folder and 2 soft cover reports (Box 674)
  - State Income Tax (Box 674)
  - State Office Building (Box 674)
  - State Police Dep[artmen]t, 3 folders (Box 674)
  - State Prison, Connecticut, 4 folders (Box 674)
  - State Prison Industries Advisory Commission (Box 674)
  - State Reservoirs, Committee to Make a Study of Public Use of – Recreational Facilities at (Box 674)
  - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of (Box 675)
  - Stevenson, Adlai, for President, 1956, 1960 (Box 675)
  - Stonington, Town of, re: Relocation of Route 1 (Box 675)
  - Suggested State Legislation – Program for 1961 (Box 675)
  - Supreme Court and State Library Building – Telephone Service (Box 675)
  - Swimming and Fishing in Tributary Streams S. B. 550 (Box 675)
  - Taborsky and Columbe – Joseph L. Taborsky and Arthur Columbe (Box 675)
  - Tarbell, Frank S. [Lieutenant, Corps of Engineers, U. S. Army] [Legion of merit for service during flood] (Box 675)
  - Taxation (Box 675)
  - Tax Department, 4 folders (Box 675)
  - Tax Study Commission (Box 675)
  - Teachers’ Retirement Board (Box 675)
  - Teachers’ Salaries (Box 675)
  - Teenage Drivers, 2 folders (Box 676)
  - Telephones [Governor’s offices] (Box 676)
  - Television Channels (VHF and UHF) [Comments and Correspondence in 1955 re: proposal by the FCC to take VHF 3 away from WTIC and assign it out of State. FCC proposed to give WTIC UHF61.] (Box 676)
  - Temporary Rent Commission (Box 676)
  - Textile Committee, New England Governors’, 3 folders (Box 676)
  - “There’s a Career for You in Conn[ecticut] Industry” [Report to Governor on booklet by the state’s four power companies] (Box 676)
  - Torrington and Winsted (Flood Control Dams re: Bond Issue of $1,750,000 Approved by the Conn[ecticut] Gen[eral] Assem[bly] Finance Committee) (Box 676)
  - Torrington Housing (Box 676)
  - Traffic Commission (State) (Box 676)
  - Traffic Safety, Regional Conference, Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1956 May 1-2 (Box 676)
  - Traffic Safety, the President’s Committee For, 2 folders (Box 676)
  - Traffic School (experimental) for “Teen-Age” traffic violators: (Baltimore Plan) (Judge J. J. Salman) (Box 676)
  - Transportation, Public, New England Governors’ Conference, Committee on, 3 folders (Box 676)
  - Treasurer, State, 8 folders (Box 677)
    Carbon copies of monthly financial reports.
  - Tree Protection Examining Board (Box 677)
  - Truck Traffic re: G[reenwich] – K[illingly] Turnpike and Center Road Bridge (Box 677)
  - Trumbull High School re: Site Situation, Trumbull, Conn[ecticut] (Box 677)
  - Tuberculosis & Other Chronic Illness, Commission on (Box 677)
  - Tuberculosis Commission (Box 677)
  - Tuberculosis Commission re: Undercliff Hospital Transfer [of Patients to other Sanitoria] (Box 677)
  - Tully and O’Brien [Two individuals connected to U-CONN arrested in the Philippines for union activities. Includes photographs.] (Box 677)
  - Typewriters re: Imposition of a Tariff on the Importation of (Box 677)
  - Undercliff Hospital (Box 677)
  - Underwood Corporation [re: Governor’s assistance to] (Box 677)
  - Unemployment, 4 folders (Box 678)
  - Unemployment – Letters from Claimants for Unemployment Compensation, 2 folders (Box 678)
  - Unemployment Compensation (Box 678)
  - Unemployment Compensation Commissioner – 2nd Congressional District (Box 678)
  - Unemployment Situation in Connecticut – Meeting – Legislative Leaders with Gov[ernor] Ribicoff and Unemployment Compensation, 1958 February 20 (Box 678)
  - Uniform Commercial Code (Box 678)
  - United Aircraft Corporation: (Strike Material) (Box 678)
  - United States Coast Guard Academy Buildings (New London, Conn[ecticut]) [Publicity re: Academy needs and resulting controversy] (Box 678)
  - U. S. Senators, Washington [D. C.] (Box 678)
  - University of Connecticut, 2 folders (Box 678)
  - University of Connecticut, 4 folders (Box 679)
  - University of Hartford [Founder’s Dinner], 1958 (Box 679)
  - Vesicular Exanthema [Swine disease], 1955 (Box 679)
  - Veterans Affairs, Committee on [S. R. 19] (Box 679)
  - Veterans Home and Hospital (Box 679)
  - Veterinary Registration and Examination, Board of (Box 679)
  - Veto Messages – Gov[ernor] Ribicoff (Box 679)
  - Wage Reporting Method (Box 679)
  - Wallingford – Detour of Route 5 (Box 679)
  - Wallingford Railroad Crossing (Box 679)
  - Watch Industry (Box 679)
  - Waterbury, City of re: Proposal to turn over to the State of Conn[ecticut] land and buildings of the Waterbury Branch, Univ[ersity] of Conn[ecticut] (Box 679)
  - Waterbury Expressway (Box 679)
  - Waterbury Housing Authority (Box 679)
  - Waterbury Police Dep[artmen]t, Motor Vehicle Law School (Box 679)
  - Water Resources Commission (Box 679)
  - Wauregan Mills, Inc. (Box 679)
  - Weather Modification Research (Dr. Thomas F. Malone, Traveler’s; George R. Rumney, Ass[istan]t Prof[essor] of Geography, at Univ[ersity] of Conn[ecticut], Storrs) (Box 680)
  - WBZ Radio Station, Boston, Mass[achusetts] (Box 680)
  - Weekly Newspapers (Box 680)
  - Welfare Department, 4 folders (Box 680)
  - Wesleyan University, Purchase of Long Lane School from State of Connecticut [Attorney General’s Opinion Against] (Box 680)
  - Wessell [,Frank, Executive Clerk?] (Box 680)
  - Wessell Dinner [retirement dinner] (Box 680)
  - Westcott Cove, Stamford, Conn[ecticut], Improvement of (Box 680)
  - West Hartford Charter Bill (Box 680)
  - Westinghouse Strike (Bryant Electric Co[mpany], Bridgeport, Conn[ecticut]) (Box 680)
  - Westport Pension Bill (Box 680)
  - West Virginia – Gov[ernor] William O. Marland (Box 680)
  - Wheeler Mansion Preservation Association (Bridgeport, Conn[ecticut]) (Box 680)
  - White House Conference on Highway Safety, 1954 February 17-19 (Box 680)
  - Henry Whitefield State Historical Museum (Box 680)
  - Wholesale Milk Producers’ Council (Box 680)
  - Wildlife, Preservation of (Box 680)
  - Wilton Bills – Con [Against Governor’s Veto] (Box 680)
  - Wilton Bills – Pro [For Governor’s Veto] (Box 680)
  - Wilton – Route 33, U.S. Route 7 (Box 680)
  - Woodbridge Manor Homes Development – Ansonia, Conn[ecticut] (Box 680)
  - Woodruff Hospital (New Haven, Conn[ecticut]) (Box 680)
  - Wood Screws, Tariff on (Box 681)
  - Workmen’s Compensation Commission (Box 681)
  - Yale Corporation, 3 folders (Box 681)
  - “Yankee Homecoming” (Jack Frost) [President of event] (Box 681)
  - Young, Richard v. John J. Tynan, Commissioner of Motor Vehicles re: Suspension of License for Speeding (Box 681)
- Series 3. Flood of 1955 Files
  Contains material pertaining to the Flood of 1955 and its aftermath. The reason that these files are not within the previously listed subject files is not known. Researchers should be aware that the files in the following boxes are not listed in alphabetical order. Staff has retained the order in which they were originally listed.
  - Flood: Deaths and Operation “Noah” (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: A (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: BA – COL (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: COL – DAN (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: DAR – FIE (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: FIE – FZ (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: GA – HOT (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: HOU – LA (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: LA – MER (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: MES – NE (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: NE – PL (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: PL – RO (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: RO – SN (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: SO – TR (Box 682)
  - Flood [Correspondence]: TR – Z (Box 682)
  - Flood: Commerce, Dep[artmen]t of – Handbook on Flood Damage Assistance Available from U. S. Government (Box 682)
  - Flood: Contributions Received by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff re: Flood Relief Fund (Box 682)
  - Flood: Contributions Received re: Flood Relief Fund, 2 folders (Box 683)
  - Flood: Contributions Received re: Flood Relief Acknowledged (Box 683)
  - Flood: Financing Program of Flood Recovery (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Disaster Insurance [Federal publication and 1 folder] (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Mortgage Loans, Home Ownership (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Taxes (Box 683)
  - Flood: Miscellaneous Material, 2 folders (Box 683)
  - Flood, Prevention of (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Warning Organization for New England By the U.S.Weather Bureau, Bradley Field (Conn[ecticut] River Watershed Council) (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Warning and Protection System Meeting by Governor Ribicoff, 1956 March 21 (Box 683)
  - Flood: Desilting of Rivers in Connecticut – Plans for Cleaning and (Box 683)
  - Flood Protection (Box 683)
  - Flood: Flood Control, Rivers and Harbors and Beach Erosion Projects in Conn[ecticut] (Box 683)
  - Flood: Baltic Flood Prevention, Correspondence re: (S – 497) (Box 683)
  - Flood: Manual for Conn[ecticut] Flood Recovery Program, 1956 (Box 683)
  - Flood Praise: Letters rec[eive]d by Gov[ernor] Ribicoff (Box 683)
  - Flood: Offers of Assistance and Sympathy (Box 683)
  - Flood: Press Releases on Flood Control [Not Foldered] (Box 683)
  - Flood: Army Engineers [Corps of] (Box 684)
  - Flood: Anniversary, 2nd, Reports, Clippings – Editorials (Box 684)
  - Flood: Control – Conn[ecticut] (Box 684)
  - Flood: Control – Eisenhower Veto (Box 684)
  - Flood: Control – General Assembly – 1957 Session (Box 684)
  - Flood: Control – Rooster River (Box 684)
  - Flood: Danbury (Box 684)
  - Flood: Farmington Valley (Box 684)
  - Flood: [Restoration of Federal Funds] (Box 684)
  - Flood: Highways (Box 684)
  - Flood: Industry (Box 684)
  - Flood: Knapp Committee Report (Box 684)
  - Flood: Naugatuck (Box 684)
  - Flood: New Haven Railroad (Box 684)
  - Flood: Norwalk (Box 684)
  - Flood: Planning (Box 684)
  - Flood: Putnam (Box 684)
  - Flood: Red Cross (Box 684)
  - Flood: Recovery (Box 684)
  - Flood: Report to the General Assembly, January 30, 1957 (Box 684)
  - Flood: Reports (Box 684)
  - Flood: Statistics (Box 684)
  - Flood Control Dam – Thomaston (Box 684)
  - Flood Control Dam – Torrington (Box 684)
  - Flood Control Dam – Warning (Box 684)
  - Flood Control Dam – Washington (Box 684)
  - Flood: Waterbury (Box 684)
  - Flood: Winsted Clippings (Box 684)
  - Flood: Winsted 1956 Proceedings of the National Association of Insurance Commissioners, Vol II William G. Hoyt and Walter B. Lanbein, Floods (Princeton, NJ: Princeton University Press, 1955). (Box 684)
  - Flood: Report of the Conn[ecticut] Flood Recovery Committee to Governor Abraham Ribicoff, 1955 November 3; 2 copies (Box 685)
  - Flood: After Action Narrative and Report, Flood of August 1955, 3 copies (Box 685)